iOS Software Engineer

ANDREY YASTREBOV

me@ayastrebov.com

+7 (931) 221 24

12

ayastrebov.com

G AYastrebov

EXPERIENCE

Mail.ru (Odnoklassniki)

iOS Software Engineer | since May 2016

Member of Odnoklassniki iOS core team.

Luxoft

Lead iOS Software Engineer | June 2015 - April 2016

Developing iOS apps for Tinkoff bank.

Agile Fusion Corporation

iOS Software Engineer | July 2012 - June 2015

Developing iOS apps for U.S. customers.

FoodMap LLC

iOS and Android Software Engineer, Co-founder | May 2011 - June 2012

iOS and Android app for spotting nearest cafes and restaurants and provides a full menu with a social integration.

Lanit-Tercom

iOS Software Engineer | September 2010 - May 2011

Developing iOS apps.

EDUCATION

Saint-Petersburg State University, Mathematics and Mechanics Faculty.

Specialist (Information technologies) | 2006 - 2012

SKILLS

I am constantly learning new technologies and always try to improve my skills in this rapidly changing industry.

About me

Senior iOS Software Engineer with more than 10 years of experience creating complex, user-focused software applications at the highest level of quality and efficiency. Started developing since iOS 3.0 in Objective-C and recently switched to Swift.